[
    { "question": "SSH (Secure Shell)", "answer": "22", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "DNS (Domain Name System)", "answer": "53", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SFTP (SSH File Transfer Protocol)", "answer": "22", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "FTP (File Transfer Protocol)", "answer": "20, 21", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "TFTP (Trivial File Transfer Protocol)", "answer": "69", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "Telnet (Teletype Network)", "answer": "23", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "DHCP (Dynamic Host Configuration Protocol)", "answer": "67, 68", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "HTTP (Hypertext Transfer Protocol)", "answer": "80", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "HTTPS (Hypertext Transfer Protocol Secure)", "answer": "443", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "HTTPS (TLS)", "answer": "443", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SNMP (Simple Network Management Protocol)", "answer": "161, 162", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "RDP (Remote Desktop Protocol)", "answer": "3389", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "NTP (Network Time Protocol)", "answer": "123", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SIP (Session Initiation Protocol)", "answer": "5060â€“5061", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SMB (Server Message Block)", "answer": "445", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SMTP (Simple Mail Transfer Protocol)", "answer": "25", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SMTP (TLS)", "answer": "587", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "POP / POP3 (Post Office Protocol)", "answer": "110", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "POP3 (TLS)", "answer": "995", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "IMAP (Internet Message Access Protocol)", "answer": "143", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "IMAP (SSL)", "answer": "993", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "LDAP (Lightweight Directory Access Protocol)", "answer": "389", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "LDAPS (Lightweight Directory Access Protocol Secure)", "answer": "636", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "Syslog", "answer": "514", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SQL Server", "answer": "1433", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "SQLnet (Oracle)", "answer": "1521", "knowledge level": 0 },
    { "question": "MySQL", "answer": "3306", "knowledge level": 0 }
  ]
  